import { quizDataProps } from "@/types/quiz-data";

export const mathsQuizData: quizDataProps[] = [
  {
    question:
      "What is next in the following number series: 256, 289, 324, 361 . . . ?",
    answers: ["400", "200", "800", "600"],
    correct: "400",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of a triangle that has two sides of the same length?",
    answers: ["Equilateral", "Scalene", "Isosceles", "Right-angled"],
    correct: "Isosceles",
  },
  {
    question: "How many vertices are present on a cube?",
    answers: ["6", "8", "10", "14"],
    correct: "8",
  },
  {
    question: "Calculate the HCF of 1.08, 0.36 and 0.9.",
    answers: ["0.03", "0.9", "0.18", "0.108"],
    correct: "0.18",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the least number which is exactly divisible by 6, 12, 9 and 18?",
    answers: ["96", "36", "24", "81"],
    correct: "36",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the perimeter of a square with a side length of 5 units?",
    answers: ["20 units", "25 units", "15 units", "10 units"],
    correct: "20 units",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If a rectangle has a length of 8 units and a width of 5 units, what is its area?",
    answers: [
      "40 square units",
      "30 square units",
      "13 square units",
      "50 square units",
    ],
    correct: "40 square units",
  },
  {
    question: "If you divide 56 by 7, what is the quotient?",
    answers: ["8", "7", "9", "6"],
    correct: "8",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the sum of the interior angles of a triangle?",
    answers: ["180 degrees", "360 degrees", "90 degrees", "270 degrees"],
    correct: "180 degrees",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between 100 and 37?",
    answers: ["63", "73", "67", "83"],
    correct: "63",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the product of 12 and 11?",
    answers: ["132", "121", "144", "110"],
    correct: "132",
  },
  {
    question: "If a circle has a radius of 7 units, what is its diameter?",
    answers: ["14 units", "21 units", "7 units", "28 units"],
    correct: "14 units",
  },
  {
    question: "How many sides does a hexagon have?",
    answers: ["6", "5", "7", "8"],
    correct: "6",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the next number in the sequence: 2, 6, 12, 20, ?",
    answers: ["30", "28", "32", "24"],
    correct: "30",
  },
  {
    question: "How many degrees are in a right angle?",
    answers: ["90 degrees", "180 degrees", "45 degrees", "360 degrees"],
    correct: "90 degrees",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of subtracting 7 from 20?",
    answers: ["13", "15", "12", "14"],
    correct: "13",
  },
];
